## **Jordan Dunbar**

Glasgow 07887695529

<u>JordanDunbar23@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/JDunbar23</u>

## **SUMMARY**

Student in Software Development with experience and extensive education in software design and development. Excellent verbal and written communication due to years of customer service. A fast learner with strong time management, multi tasking skills and strong work ethic in a team or individually. Strong troubleshooting and problem solving skills with an analytical mindset.

## **SKILLS**

Languages: C#, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS

Tools: Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, PowerBI, MS Office (Excel,

Word, Powerpoint, Outlook, Access), Visio, AutoCAD Other: T-SQL, SSIS, SSRS, SSAS, DBMS, RDBMS

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Delivery Driver**

#### Pizza Hut

#### March 2018 to December 2018

- Delivered products in a timely manner and collected payments from customers.
- Resolved customers enquiries about products and services.
- Maintained health & safety standards within the store.

#### <u>Customer Service Advisor</u>

#### **Harpercollins Publishers**

## May 2017 to August 2017

- Coordinated paperwork and payments for new orders and replacement books to obtain speedy service for each customer.
- Conferred with customers about concerns with products or services to resolve problems and drive sales.
- Maintained accurate and current customer account data with manual forms processing and digital information updates.

#### **Design Engineer**

#### Siemens

#### November 2016 to March 2017

- Reviewed design requirements and identified appropriate materials to use in development of solutions.
- Created CAD models and drawings for railway station platforms.
- Performed on-site field surveys and wrote technical narratives to document processes and design changes.
- Interacted with project leaders and stakeholders to define requirements and generate and maintain design development documents.

## Junior Engineer

#### **Linbrooke Services**

## September 2014 to August 2016

- Worked closely with the senior engineers drawing schematics and designing the layout for new builds on station platforms using AutoCAD.
- Applied engineering methods for sound product design to manage understandable execution of calculations and best practices.
- Performed on-site field surveys and wrote technical narratives to document processes and design changes.

#### **Desktop Technician**

## **Conservatory Climate Control**

## April 2013 to August 2014

- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Collaborated with vendors to locate replacement components and resolve advanced problems.
- Removed malware, ransomware and other threats from laptops and desktop systems.

#### **Stockroom Assistant**

#### Next

#### November 2012 to April 2013

- Verified quantity and description of materials received by checking merchandise against the packing list.
- Recorded information, shortages and discrepancies to keep records current and accurate.
- Kept warehouse clean and organized to maximize team efficiency and productivity.
- Moved furniture and boxes using utility dolly and truck ramp.

#### **Sales Assistant**

#### **Primark**

#### January 2008 to September 2012

- Delivered a high level of assistance by locating products and checking store systems for merchandise at other sites.
- Collaborated with managers to provide customer feedback and recommend operational changes to meet emerging trends.
- Referred customers to various services by evaluating needs and providing recommendations.
- Refunded payments for returned items, processed exchanges and offered store credit to achieve customer satisfaction.
- Processed cash, check and credit card payments.

## **EDUCATION**

# Bsc Video Game Software Development Glasgow Caledonian University 2018 to 2021

HNC Video Game Development
City of Glasgow College
2017 to 2018

HNC Computing
City of Glasgow College
2012 to 2013

HNC Civil Engineering
Stow College
2008 to 2009

Stonelaw High School 2003 to 2008

Int 1 Maths - A
Int 1 Music - A
Int 1 Technical Studies - B
Int 2 English - C